{
    "id": "72105760770044a3b736d462a3d1ad18",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… jeered at the thief.",
            "description": "When a pronoun is the subject of the verb, we use the nominative form.",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "Them"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There was no way for ……………………….. to escape.",
            "description": "The object form of the pronoun is used after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Between you and …………………………, I don’t trust him.",
            "description": "The object form of the pronoun is used after a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Give …………………………. the keys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… cooked dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly an idea struck ………………………….",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a verb should be in the object form.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. will bell the cat?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The deer looked at …………………………… reflection in the water.",
            "description": "Its is a possessive word like his or her.",
            "answers": [
                "it",
                "its",
                "it's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You could have killed ………………………….",
            "description": "When the subject and object refer to the same person, the reflexive pronoun is used for the object. ",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Prospero assured ………………………….. that ………………………… ship was safely anchored.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "them, there",
                "they, their",
                "them, their"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She told ………………………….. that …………………….. had passed the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I, me",
                "me, I",
                "me, me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They accused ……………………… of spoiling ……………………….. plans.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me, they",
                "me, their",
                "I, their"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}